

My Contact

∑ r

mailvishwadeephere@gmail.com

(1)

+91 7814092325

https://vishwadeep-s.netlify.app/

0

Kormangla, Bengaluru, 560095

Skills

- React
- Gatsby
- MUI
- Tailwind
- GSAP
- GraphQL
- Vue
- NodeJS
- NestJS
- Express
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- CosmosDB

- Netlify Functions
- Azure DevOps
- Azure Blob Storage
- Docker
- Kubernetes
- Google Maps API
- Google Images
- API Keyvault
- Github
- Auth0
- Keycloak
- Azure Functions

Education

2014 - 2016

Lovely Professional University Btech (ECE) - Dropped Out

Languages

English, Hindi

Vishwadeep Singh

Full Stack Developer

About Me

I believe that there is always a room for improvements regardless of one's level of expertise. These improvements can only be brought by trying new things and making mistakes while doing it. Learning from mistakes and having a positive attitude is the key to growth. I am also a technology believer and I believe that a better place for everyone can be achieved with advancements in tech.

Professional Experience

SleekSky | Software Development Engineer

08/2022 - CURRENT

- Worked on implementing in house translations on backend.
- Helped improve performance of analytics functions and decreased response time by 80%.
- Lead design and development of backends using Nest.js.
- Helped to create interactive UI for JSON editor using React.
- Worked on developing data driven site using EJS.
- Implemented payment method with Stripe on Node server.
- Helped setting up CI/CD with docker and kubernatics.

FlockAlong | Web Developer

12/2020 - 08/2022

- While at FlockAlong, I worked with Gatsby, Nodejs, Netlify Functions, C#, Auth0, Google Maps, Algolia, Cypress.
- I was responsible for developing Gatsby based Front-End which served as a platform for customers to create, join and manage trips.
- Helped developing parts of Back-End wriiten in C# and Node.
- Implemented Algolia search engine and automated data upload/update to Algolia servers
- Implemented authentication/authorization flow with Auth0.

KhaoBao | Operations Manager

12/2018 - 11/2019

- I was responsible for development of Android Apps Customer Side and Delivery Guy app.
- In parallel I was handling day to day operations including signing new restaurants, improving customer experience and launching new services.
- Completed 40k successful orders over a period of more than 14 months.